Rochester (NY) Federation of Classroom Teachers Records 5853
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Rochester (NY) Federation of Classroom Teachers Records
1955-1969
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Rochester (NY) Federation of Classroom Teachers
5853
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Some records of the Rochester Federation of Classroom Teachers.
5713675
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 12, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Scope and Contents
Part of the "Van Arsdale Project"
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Teachers' unions, New York (State), Rochester; Van Arsdale, Harry, 1905-1986; Federation of Classroom Teachers (Rochester, N.Y.)
5713675
- Catherine Sheehan Teacher Certification, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Catherine Sheehan Retirement Correspondence, 1954-1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Photographs of Catherine Sheehan (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Newsletters, 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Request for Grievance Procedures, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Letters to the Edition of the Times Union, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Leonard Schieffelin, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 16)
- News Clippings, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- News Clippings, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- News Clippings (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Federation Teacher, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- NY State Senate and Assembly Bills, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- NYSTA News, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Minutes of Rochester Federation of Classroom Teachers, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Testimonial Dinner for Catherine Sheehan, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Rochester Civic Music Association, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Spring Conference, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Rochester Board of Education Correspondence, 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Insurance, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Political Memo From COPE, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Carl J. Megel Merit Pay Statement, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- American Federation of Teachers Local 616, 1948-1958 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- U.S. Congress, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- U.S. Congress Jacob Javits, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Investigation of Low Morale at Edison High School, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Federation of Reporter, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Irish Writers and Others, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- A Study of Various Proposals for Liberalizing The New York State Teachers Retirement System, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- John Keenan Re-election as President of Rochester Board of Education (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Notes on Newspaper Articles, 1952-1954 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- John Marshall High School, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Social Security, 1954-1957 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Report of the Academic Teacher Certification Project, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- New York State Education, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Legislative Bulletin, 1952-1958 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Rochester Federation of Classroom Teachers Letter Head (Box 1, Folder 46)
- American Federation of Teachers Pamphlets, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- The American Teacher, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Changed Attitudes Change Everything, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Rochester Federation of Teachers Constitution, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Empire State Federation of Teachers, 1953-1964 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- International Federation of Free Teachers Unions, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Bureau of Educational Research, News Letter, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Schoolways, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- New York State Teachers' Association Elections (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Miscellaneous Notes and Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Constitutional Convention News Clippings, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Constitutional Convention News Clippings, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Constitutional Convention News Clippings, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Rochester Federation of Teachers News Clippings, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Board of Education News Clippings, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Rochester Federation of Teachers Resolution, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Rochester School Meeting, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Rochester Teachers' Pension and Retirement Plans, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Rochester Schools' Easter Vacation News Clippings, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- New York State Teachers' Association Pamphlet, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Science in High Schools, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Rochester BOE Politics News Clippings, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- R.T.A. Salary Committee Report, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Problems with Albany Schools News Clippings, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- R.T.A. House of Representatives Meeting and Bulletin, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Troth's Fortune Maryland (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Boston Cliff Maryland (Box 2, Folder 17)
- New York State Teachers Association Legislative Bulletin, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Rochester BOE Letters, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Teachers' Salaries News Clippings, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Teachers' Salaries News Clippings, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Teachers' Salaries News Clippings, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Teachers' Salaries News Clippings, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Teachers' Salaries News Clippings, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Teachers' Salaries News Clippings, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Teachers' Salaries News Clippings, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Teachers' Salaries News Clippings, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- James L. Burke's Letters, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Women's Politics, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Board of Education Blasted By Corsall, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Bob Wagner Rally News Clippings (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Sheehan and the Labor Council, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Why Our Teachers Can't Retire, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Why Our Teachers Can't Retire, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Letter to Senator Van Lane, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Teachers Negotiations, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Teachers Negotiations, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Drop in Teachers' Morale, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Charlotte Faculty Attacks Education Board, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Board Scans Teachers Pay Requests, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Teachers Union News Clippings, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Teachers Union News Clippings, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Teachers Union News Clippings, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Oswego Mayor, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Legislative Bulletin No.1-3, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Teachers Voting on Social Security News Clippings, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- GOP School Plan, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Fresh School Approach, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Sick Teachers, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Madison Incident, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Fraternity Ban, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- 25.5 Million Plan For Scholarships Urged by Regents, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Hiring of Teachers on a 12-Month Basis Urged By Seymour, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Union Procedures, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Union Elections, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- 'Discipline' - Commissioner Ott, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Time for Teaching, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Future Expectations, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Study of Teacher Fund System, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Problems Teachers Are Facing, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Local Split Debate City Principal in Teacher Vote, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- President Burke's Letter to Culver Barr, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Editorial On Pampering, School Shortage, and the Edison Expansion Plan, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Teachers Pensions Drop, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Teachers Association In 'United Front' Move, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Teachers Ask For Pay Increase At Council Meeting, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Board Debates Pay Schedule, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Teachers Pay Raised, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Teachers Pay Raised, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Sales Tax, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Sales Tax, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Rochester Classroom Teachers Organization Merger with Union, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Council Promises School Board Funds, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- School Poverty Threat to Democracy, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Teacher Pay Group, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- Teachers Negotiating Committee, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- City Teachers Get To Pay Hike, State Funds To Defray Cost, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 77)
- City Teachers Ask Democrats To Back Retirement Benefits, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Consider the Lilies, of Glass, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Teachers Misled on Tax Increase, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 80)
- School Services Tied to New Funds, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Teachers Association Backs $700 In United Move, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Teachers Unite On $700 Boost, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 83)
- School Spending; Tax Increases, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 84)
- School Meeting On Teachers Pay, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 85)
- No Raise for Teachers, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 86)
- John Marshall High School Faculty Letter to the BOE, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 87)
- "Teachers Speak" News Editorial (Box 2, Folder 88)
- "Need Teacher Pay Study, Officials Say", 1955 (Box 2, Folder 89)
- Teachers Meeting Ousts Vice-Mayor, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Democrats Demand Sales Tax Increase, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 91)
- "City Employees Pay Hikes Recommended to Council", 1956 (Box 2, Folder 92)
- Board Adopts New Salary Schedule, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 93)
- The Ruml Report on Schedule (Box 2, Folder 94)
- "Why School Board Votes 'No' On Salary Boost for Teachers", 1955 (Box 2, Folder 95)
- "School Meeting First Calm, Then Lively", 1956 (Box 2, Folder 96)
- Teachers Respond to Commissioner Wolz, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 97)
- "Brilliance Can Be Recruited for Public School Teaching" (Box 2, Folder 98)
- "City Schools Rapped for Fiscal Practices", 1958 (Box 2, Folder 99)
- "How Satellite Battle Was Lost" (Box 2, Folder 100)
- Letters Regarding Teacher Recruitment, 1956-1958 (Box 2, Folder 101)
- Recommendation 4 (Box 2, Folder 102)
- News On Cite Merger and Unemployment Benefits, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 103)
- Proposed Salary Schedule, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 104)
- School Interruptions, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 105)
- Special Bulletin On The Distribution of State Aid To Education Challenged, 1954-1958 (Box 2, Folder 106)
- "Why Our Teachers 'Cannot Retire'" (Box 2, Folder 107)
- Democracy in Education, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 108)
- Empire State Federation of Teachers, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 109)
- Teachers' Bill of Rights, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 110)
- NYSTA "Professional Practice Act", 1956-1958 (Box 2, Folder 111)
- Report of Meeting in Dr. Seymour's Office", 1956 (Box 2, Folder 112)
- Catherine Sheehan Letters, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 113)
- Catherine Sheehan Elected President of Rochester Classroom Teachers Organization, 1950-1954 (Box 2, Folder 114)
- City Teachers Elect Delegates, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 115)
- Problems of Discipline, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 116)
- Re O'Rourke Papers, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 117)
- Material from RIA and Thomistic Theses (Box 2, Folder 118)
- Teachers Union Elect Officials, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 119)
- 'Firetrap' Schools, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 120)
- The Board on Teacher Financial Policies, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 121)
- "Citizens' Group Blocked, First President Charge", 1957 (Box 2, Folder 122)
- Rochester High School Guidance and Counseling Practices, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 123)
- Posner Pushes for Colleges; Catherine Sheehan, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 124)
- Teacher Morale Survey, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 125)
- "What Is Tenure'"?, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 126)
- "City vs. County College", 1960 (Box 2, Folder 127)
- "Probe of School Guidance Urged", 1960 (Box 2, Folder 128)
- The Dismissal of William C. Olsen, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 129)
- School Grievance Unit, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 130)
- Teachers HR Unit, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 131)
- Teacher Union Protests, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 132)
- Morale Study, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 133)
- Olsen Issue, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 134)
- Julian L. Lowell Letter on ATA, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 135)
- Citizens Want Answers to the Olsen Case (Box 2, Folder 136)
- Social Aid Bill, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 137)
- Edison Principal Ousted, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 138)
- Edison Principal Ousted, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 139)
- Edison Principal Ousted, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 140)
- Community College, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 141)
- Community College, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 142)
- Teachers Graduate Programs and Health Insurance, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 143)
- Teachers Health Insurance, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 144)
- Community College, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 145)
- Community College, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 146)
- Rochester Teachers Are Scared, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 147)
- "Board to Study Bypassed U.S. Aid", 1960 (Box 2, Folder 148)
- Election May Show Support for Olsen, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 149)
- Farbo and Navy Building, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 150)
- Cerulli on Grievances + Archbishop of San Antonio Speaks Out Newspaper, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 151)
- The Olsen Dismissal, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 152)
- Rev. Seymour's Contract, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 153)
- Re Olsen, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 154)
- Olsen, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 155)
- Olsen, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 156)
- Olsen, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 157)
- College Heads Education Article, Morale Article S+C, Folsom May Speed w Objective Standard of Promotion, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 158)
- Olsen, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 159)
- NYSTA RTA Reports + NYSTA Journal, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 160)
- Re Teachers' Reporting Others, Letter re Court Case, Social Workers, Governor Sees Need for More College Facilities, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 161)
- Community College, A7CT 1960 Election (Box 2, Folder 162)
- Community College (Nassau County), J-U on Community College, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 163)
- School Board Meeting Editorial, NAACP on Council, Community Council, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 164)
- J-U Editorial on Budget Mrs. Nugent's Felles in Eastridge, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 165)
- Community College, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 166)
- Howe on Labor, Budget OK, Penfield Sued, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 167)
- NYSTA - Legislative Bulletin, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 168)
- AFL-CIO Aging Plant Community Editorial, K.L. Sullivan's Letter, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 169)
- Longer School Day, Holcomb's Article, Editorial, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 170)
- AFL-CIO, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 171)
- Dr. Radebaugh's Letter, City Budget, School Repairs Made, No Tax Hike for Salary Schedule, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 172)
- Penfield Case, Throngb, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 173)
- Newspaper Articles Related to School Budget and Teachers+ Fire and Police Issues Supported By Democrats, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 174)
- Re Resignations - Longer School Day, Request for Pension Plank in Democratic Platform, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 175)
- Re Salary Schedule, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 176)
- Board Urged With Separate Salary + Cangen School Day Issues + Letters from People, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 177)
- Proposed Salary Schedule, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 178)
- Re tangent School Day, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 179)
- J-U 4-1-60 Re Salary Schedule, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 180)
- School Salary Tights Marshall Letters Barry Pay Little for City Employees, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 181)
- Storm Brewing Over School Issues, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 182)
- D+C - J-U 4-4-60 Re Salary Fight, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 183)
- Teachers' Salaries D+C - J-U, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 184)
- P.B Letter Readers With Eastridge, Governor Signs State and Bill, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 185)
- D+C Harvey Granite's Letter re Longer School Day, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 186)
- J. Farbo on Budget, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 187)
- AFL-CIO, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 188)
- D+C Pupils in Teachers' College Poorer?, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 189)
- Penfield Teachers (Miller+ Korpeck) Barred From Meeting, Tom Miller's Letter, Congress aid SS Doors, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 190)
- Board of Education-1960 (Box 2, Folder 191)
- Human Relations + Political Action, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 192)
- Board of Ed. Appointment, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 193)
- Salary Longer School Day Gitelman Praised by B.7. Roral, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 194)
- Re Seymour's Contact, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 195)
- Re Shorter School Day, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 196)
- J-U Re Pay Scale, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 197)
- D+C Normal at City-Council in D+C, Re Pay Scale, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 198)
- Re Grievance Procedure, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 199)
- Forand Bill Weis Ostertag, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 200)
- The Forand Bill Mr. F France Mr. Storandt, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 201)
- Seymour Contradictions- Free Books, Book Rental Raised, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 202)
- Re Grievance + Morale Survey my letter, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 203)
- Re Certification Equalization Rate Retirement Election, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 204)
- NYS/AM "Better Use of School Year," John Cobb on Education, William Ringle on Hours of Teaching, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 205)
- Norman's Letter, Kay Sullivan's Letter, Ross Rito's Letter My Letters in Support of Norman's Articles, Article on Dr. Cerulli, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 206)
- de Kiewiet on Education, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 207)
- Letters re Court Case D+C and J-U CE x Ua Clippings. Clipping re Caseworkers, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 208)
- Insurance Fiasco, A 7 e T Regent, Letter on Court Case, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 209)
- Teachers Ask Pay Increase at Council D+C T-U PTA Meeting, Announcement of PTA Panel D+C, 1955-1958 (Box 2, Folder 210)
- Labor News County Recap Our Own Defense Fund, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 211)
- Community College, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 212)
- The Grievance Community Giangiobbe + Paul Dupre, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 213)
- Community College L-N, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 214)
- Community College, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 215)
- Community College Norman's Letters, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 216)
- Mar Zuller on Edison Battle of Books, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 217)
- Orden + Aport on Olsen, Merring Going, De Zafra of m Olsen, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 218)
- Nov-Dec. Issue of ES 7. Search 1968 (Box 2, Folder 219)
- Five Teachers Demand Increase, Labor Meeting, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 220)
- Doc. Editorial on Home Econ. Classes at Madison and Supreme fiscal independence, 1954-1958 (Box 2, Folder 221)
- We Support Merring's Use of Labor Bill, My Letters Re Harriman Veto, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 222)
- Our Plan + Help Chinese Prisoners Father McKeon S.J.M. Teachers' Rights, 1956-1958 (Box 2, Folder 223)
- Board of Education Re Survey, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 224)
- Our Grievance Procedure, On Class Interruptions, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 225)
- J-U D+C- On More Money for Education, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 226)
- Re Salary Re Rejection of Our Grievance Procedure, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 227)
- Longer School Day (Box 2, Folder 228)
- Poets, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 229)
- Antiques Castleford - Gaudy Dutch (Box 2, Folder 230)
- Father Flood's Poetry, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 231)
- Antiques - Sandwich Glass, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 232)
- Olsen Care, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 233)
- Portables, Dwindling Contingency Fund, Gitelman on Tax Rate, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 234)
- Norman on Coercion Norman Aid For Service, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 235)
- Re Sick Leave Re NY Salary Fight, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 236)
- Re Grievance R Wade's Article, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 237)
- Seymour on Child Labor Law Burke Election, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 238)
- Asian Flue Fight, Flu, Grievance Council The Refined. East High, 1957-1959 (Box 2, Folder 239)
- Seymour Re Staff, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 240)
- Democrats' Support, Labor Support, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 241)
- Democrats' Say Pay Raise Best Issue, PTA Meeting, Pay Rise Said Doomed, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 242)
- Farbo Ousted From Meeting, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 243)
- George Cook on Pay Rise, Letters From Laurels, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 244)
- My Resignation as A7 CT Federation, Budget Hearing, Labor News, American Teacher re my election as Treasurer of Central Trades, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 245)
- Salary Fights, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 246)